{
  "LevelId": 71,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 725,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BUBBLEGUM",
      "question": "the chewy and elastic confection,"
    },
    {
      "id": 726,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CIGARETTE",
      "question": "narrow cylinder of finely cut tobacco leaves that is rolled into thin paper for smoking"
    },
    {
      "id": 727,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CLASSROOM",
      "question": "designated space within a school where students gather for educational instruction,"
    },
    {
      "id": 728,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BARKEEPER",
      "question": "person responsible for managing and serving drinks at a bar,"
    },
    {
      "id": 729,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "DANEWORTS",
      "question": "plants or herbs, historically believed to have magical or protective properties,"
    },
    {
      "id": 730,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "EMPTINESS",
      "question": "the state of being vacant or devoid of content,"
    },
    {
      "id": 731,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "CELEBRATE",
      "question": "the action of publicly acknowledging and enjoying a significant event, achievement,"
    },
    {
      "id": 732,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "DOGNAPPER",
      "question": "who engages in the unlawful act of kidnapping or stealing dogs, often for ransom or personal gain"
    },
    {
      "id": 733,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "GASOLINES",
      "question": "flammable liquid derived from petroleum,"
    },
    {
      "id": 734,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "GRIDLOCKS",
      "question": "the situation in traffic when vehicles are severely congested"
    },
    {
      "id": 735,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "BASKETBALL",
      "question": "two teams of five players each, aiming to score points by shooting a ball through the opponent's basket"
    }
  ]
}